我的命在你手里
My life is in your hands.
LJ和莎拉怎样了?
How's LJ? how's Sara?
她死了 迈克
She's dead, Michael.
我骗了你
I lied to you.
索菲亚·鲁果
Sofia Lugo
我是詹姆斯·惠斯勒的女友
I'm James Whistler's girlfriend.
我要你从这越狱 斯科菲尔德先生
You are breaking out of this prison, mr. Scofield,
并且带上我
And you're taking me with you.
再过四天
Four more days.
我就会从这出去了
If I'm out of here by then,
我能行的
I can still do it.
在过去的两天内
There ve been two escape attempts
出现了两次试图越狱行为
In the past two days.
和索纳说再见吧 斯科菲尔德先生
Say good-bye to Sona, mr. Scofield.
到了 我们单独谈下
Right there. Leave us.
我的前任 艾斯伽米上校
My predecessor, colonel Escamilla,
工作干得不够好
Wasn't an effective leader.
因此被替换了
He's been replaced.
我是萨瓦拉狱官
I am general Zavala.
坐吧
Sit.
要喝水么?
A drink of water?
尊敬的狱官阁下 这次越狱事件
With all due respect, general, I had nothing to do
跟我无关
With what happened here today.
我的调查向来细致入微
I always conduct a thorough investigation,
但这里有太多的疑问要解决
And there are too many unanswered questions here.
我的任务就是去把这些都搞清楚
It is my job to find those answers.
如果你帮我 那我也会帮你
If you help me do my job, I'll help you.
那架直升机
The helicopters.
不是你所能够弄到的
You alone couldn't be responsible for that.
那直升机
You certainly weren't
-应该与你无关 是吧? -是的
Flying a helicopter, were you? no.
-和谁有关? -我不知道
Who was? I don't know.
-但你知道是谁派来的? -不知道
But you know who sent them. no.
我还是要建议
Again, be advised
你还是说实话的好
Telling the truth is in your best interest.
我说的就是实话
I am.
我们去走走
Let's go for a walk.
我知道你内心的恐惧
I understand your fears,
但是巴拿马政府不允许这样的事发生
But the republic of panama cannot allow
如果你愿意说的话
This sort of activity. if you wish to talk,
现在正是时候
Now is the time.
我会的
I would
可我已经全说了
If there wasanything left
那我别无选择了
Then you give me no choice.
过来这边
This way.
情况不妙
This isn't good.
他们要把他给蒸喽
They're putting him in the hot box.
这会很不好受的
Things are gonna get much harder for you.
你无路可走
There's no way to win.
只有合作
You must cooperate.
承认自己的行为
Confess to this escape
并且承担该受的惩罚
And face your punishment by law,
否则就等着更严重的后果
Or face a far greater punishment
在太阳下好好想想
In the panama sun.
你自己定夺吧
It's up to you.
他完了
He's done.
全完了
He's finished.
YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
最新最快字幕下载请登录：www.YYeTs.net
■
字幕：YYeTs人人影视字幕组  后期：梁良
希望我弟弟没事
I hope my brother's all right.
很痛么?
Does it hurt?
没事
It's fine.
我要去监狱那边
I'm gonna get to the prison.
我在候车室看到了新闻
I was watching the news in the waiting room.
他们确定了几具尸体的身份 但是
They identified a few bodies, but
不是他们
It wasn't them.
到那就清楚了
I'll find out when I get there.
你去么?
You want to come?
我不知道
I don't, I don't know.
在发生这么多事之后
After everything that's happened,
我都不知道怎么办了
I don't know what to think anymore.
有什么好多想的?
What more is there to think about?
詹姆斯 对任何事都有解释
James has an answer for everything,
但是没有一个解释有意义
And nothing ever makes sense.
你该停止问问题
You need to stop asking questions
而去看看事实
And just look at the facts.
我愿意相信他所说的一切
I wanted to believe everything he was saying,
而且我还是想要他出来
And I still want him to get out.
我也希望他能出来
I want him out as well.
相信我 我每天都在竭尽全力
Trust me, I've been working on this every single day.
林肯 对你所做的一切 我真的很感激
Lincoln, I really appreciate everything you have done.
你救了我的命
You saved my life.
你不必这样帮我的
You didn't have to help me like that.
不 应该的
Yeah. I did.
上车
Get in the car.
快点
Come on
我到哪 你就到哪
Everywhere I go, there you are.
回家去 索菲亚
Go home, Sofia.
我很想开车冲出大门 阿历克斯
Part of me wanted to drive right past this gate, Alex.
你不该在这里
You don't deserve to be here.
事实上 如果你考虑到所有的事 我是应得的
Actually, if you take all things into consideration I do.
谢谢
Thank you.
等下
Wait.
不用
Don't.
我父亲在矿井里
My father worked in a mine
工作了30年
For 30 years,
每天去工作他都带上这
He took this into work with him every day.
保他平安 直至退休
Kept him safe till the day he retired.
之后他把这给了我
Then he gave it to me.
我不能收下
I can't take this.
等你出来后再还我
Give it back when you get out.
保重 阿历克斯
Take care of yourself, Alex.
嗯
Yeah.
怎么 你没胆量自己亲自动手?
What? you ain't got the guts to do it yourself?
听着 在我改变主意前 给我闭嘴
This is for you, so shut up before I change my mind.
昨天之后 你也许在怀疑
After yesterday, you may be doubting
我完成协议的能力
My ability to make good on our agreement.
但你们的命仍然还有用
I need to keep you motivated.
你有1分钟时间
You have one minute.
爸爸
Dad
LJ 谢天谢地 你还活着
LJ. LJ, thank you're alive.
不 别做傻事了
No, forget about it.
你无能为力的
There's nothing to do.
总会有些漏洞之类的
There's always something
爸爸
Dad
这些家伙无处不在
These guys are thorough
他们处处跟踪你 相信我
They follow you everywhere. Trust me.
那婊子是个疯子 什么都干的出
There's nothing that bitch is crazy.
他割了莎拉的头
She cut Sara's head off.
她不能把这事办砸了 当时我在场
She cannot lost that offer. I was there.
我虽被蒙了眼 但是我听到了
I clozed my eyes but I heard.
听我说
Listen to me.
我不会失去你的 知道吗?
I could not let that happen without you, all right?
下次你看到我
The next time you see me,
一定要注意看着我
Don'take your eyes off me.
我会告诉你怎么做
I'll tell you what to do.
知道么?
All right?
时间到了
Minute's up.
你叔叔和我
Me and your uncle,
我们知道怎么做
We know what we're doing.
我们会救你出来
We're gonna get you out of this.
我爱你
I love you.
我爱你 爸爸
I love you, dad.
似乎情况不妙啊
Looks like things didn't go so well.
你应该已经出去了的
You should be gone.
你也是啊
So should you.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
还没结束呢
It's still happening.
对于迈克 我很遗憾 不过我们还是有办法的
I feel bad for Michael, but we have a way without him.
你该歇歇了
You should get some rest.
怎么出去?
What's the way?
我会歇歇的 会的 会的 等我出去后
I'll rest. I'll rest. I'll rest when I'm out.
我一定会带上你的
I won't go without you.
相信我
You have my word.
去歇歇吧
Now get some rest.
看到斯科菲尔德在那蒸笼里了吧?
You see Scofield out in that redneck sauna?
看看他还有没有办法从里面出来
Let's see if he has the oo to get out of that one.
你也有份 是吧?
You were in on it, right?
我发现你们在勒齐的周围晃动
I see you guys lurking around Lechero.
斯科菲尔德肯定想好了逃离的计划
Scofield's gotta he a plan to escape.
如果真有 那么我全然不知
If so, I know none of it.
没错 我想你也不知道
Yeah, I bet you don't.
天呐
Whoa.
鸡尾酒喝多了 吐得的到处都是啊
Too many cocktails out on the lido deck.
麻烦来了
Here comes trouble.
库拉达 把这儿清理了
Ser Criada, clean it up.
是啊 是该清理一下
Yeah, I'll get right on that.
你听到我说的了吗
You heard what I said.
我说把这儿清理了
I told you to do something.
现在就去做 清理脏东西
Now do it. cleaning up chunks
已经不再是我的工作了
Ain't in my job description anymore.
哦 情况变了
Oh, things changed.
听着 你现在听我们的指挥
You see, you answer to us now.
听着 猛男 你吓唬不了我
Hey, caveman, you don't scare me.
去吓唬别人好了
Go bug someone else.
你在这里干什么?
What are you doing here?
我来送个重要的东西
I have a special delivery.
我需要你把这个火速带进去
I need to get it in real quick.
出多少?
How much?
我出一万
I gave you ten grand.
一万是上次的价 这个给多少
Ten grand was the last one. how much for this one?
免费
No grand.
那不了 谢谢
Then no thanks.
不 别 别急
No, no no
我觉得你应该
I think you might
再好好想想
want to reconsider
把水拿给那个囚犯
Take this water to the prisoner.
为什么我去? 他根本不配喝水
Why should i? he doesn't deserve it.
我来吧
I'll do it.
兄弟
Hi, brother.
还记得我吗?
Remember me?
这样做没有用
This isn't gonna work.
快 把这个喝下去
Come on, papi, drink this.
我不能让LJ出事 明白吗?
Don't leanything happen to LJ, okay?
我明白 他的情况比你好多了
It's okay. he's doing much better than you.
快 喝下这杯 你需要的
Come on. drink this. you need it.
莎拉的事情我很抱歉
I'm sorry about Sara.
下次我试着溜进监狱更深的地方 好吗?
I'm gonna try to sneak more into the prison next time, okay?
我要你放弃
I want you to quit.
我做不到
I can't.
-我们都需要适可而止 -不 迈克
We all have to quit sometime. no, Michael.
你现在困在这个鸡笼中 你现在正是需要帮助的时刻
You're here in a chicken coop you need all the help you can get.
不需要你来帮 走吧 不要回头
Don't need your help. just go, and don't look back.
-你为我做了那么多 我不会丢下你 -走
Not after everything you've done for me.
离开这 快走吧
Just leave, go.
这么说你昨天试着搭乘直升机
So you tried to catch a flight
从这里逃出去?
Out of here yesterday?
只能这样 没有办法
I had to do wh I had to do.
没错 但是你现在回到我们的交易中
Yeah, but you went back on our deal.
我只是在帮助我自己
I was saving my own ass.
我相信你还记得计划
I'm sure you're familiar with the strategy.
现在 你听好了
Now, you watch it.
在这里我还是老大
I'm still boss here.
谁还在乎老大是谁?
Who cares about who's boss?
你还想从这里出去吗?
Do you want to get out of here,
或者你想在这里喋喋不休?
Or do you want to keep talking about it?
没事
It's okay.
我们只是需要把这块撑起来
We just need to brace it.
不 我们需要结构工程师
No. we need the engineer.
把它挪开
Move it.
萨米回来之前 我们赶快离开这里
Let's get out of here before Sammy gets back.
阴凉处华氏98度 笼子里边125度
98 degrees in the shade, 125 in the box.
让我们进去 找个空调房间
Let's go inside. we'll have a chat
好好谈谈
In the air conditioning.
明天会更热
Tomorrow is going to be hotter,
后天 就像小火炉一样
The next day, even hotter.
大后天 你就会成一具死尸
The day after that, you'll be dead.
你不明白
You don't understand.
如果我认为你能帮我
If I thought you could help me
我能够
I can.
你不明白我在这个省
You're unaware of the influence
的庞大关系网
I have in this province.
你希望我是你的盟友而不是敌人 不是吗?
You'd rather I be your ally than your enemy, wouldn't you?
你不了解这些人
You don't know these people.
我们无法阻止他们 至少你不能
We can't stop them not you,
也不是我
Not me.
曾经有个人 一个大毒枭
There was a man a drug kingpin
巴拿马最有权势的人
The most powerful man in panama.
一个冷血的杀手 身后有一只由暴徒
A ruthless killer with an army of thugs
小偷组成的军队
And thieves behind him.
他杀害法官 警察
He killed judges and policemen,
所有阻碍他的人
Anyone who stood in his way.
人们说他不可阻挡 但是现在
They said he couldn't be stopped either, but now
勒齐在监狱里 而我控制着这里
Lechero is in prison, and I'm in power.
我决定着生杀大权 现在你的命在我手中
I decide whose life is at stake, and right now, it is yours.
从我来到这儿那一刻起
From the moment I got here
我就在策划越狱
I've been planning my escape.
他说话了
He's talking.
你怎么知道?
How do you know?
要从牢笼出来 你别无选择
You can't get out of the box any other way.
派直升机来的人
The people who sent the helicopters,
他们和陷害我哥哥
They're the same people
的是同一伙人
Who framed my brother
在美国的时候
Back in the u.s.,
想把我送到索纳监狱
The same people
也是这伙人
Who wanted me here in sona.
从而帮助一名囚犯越狱?
In order for you to break out another inmate?
没错
Yes.
这些是什么人?
Who are these people?
我不知道
I don't know,
但是他们抓了我的侄子
But they have my brother's son.
他们手握人质
They like to keep collateral.
如果我开口 我可能会危及他的安全
I could be putting his life in danger as we speak.
如果你说的是实情
If what you told me is true
你可以救他
you would be saving him.
我将呼叫我的军队 并且立刻布置
I would call my troops and order a search
一次搜索行动
For the boy immediately.
但是这个故事
But this story
像小说一样
It's fiction.
这是真的
It's true.
这是你想要的
It's what you nted.
也是我唯一能够透露的了
It's the only thing I have left to give.
求求你
Please.
他的名字叫LJ
His name is LJ.
他只有16岁
He's only 16 years old.
什么味道?
What's that smell?
阿曼多雪茄
Armandos.
这次东西可不便宜
These things ct money.
有人给我的 但是我根本不抽这东西
Somebody gave them to me I don't even smoke those things.
谁? 我替他
Who? this guy i
带些东西进监狱
Ran some stuff into the prison for, man.
你捎东西进监狱? 比如说什么? 毒品?
You ran some stuff into the prison? like what? drugs?
我不知道 谁知道呢? 他付我钱
I don't kn. who cares? he paid me.
-你不该继续干那事的 -我明白了 好吗?
You should have quit that job, i I know, okay?
我需要为我的孩子弄点儿钱
I need some cash for my kid.
玛丽克鲁兹没有保险 好吗?
Maricruz doesn't have insurance, all right?
听着 我刚才看到迈克了
Listen. i I just saw Michael.
-他现在被单独囚禁 -什么?
He's in solitary confinement. what?
他们把他塞到广场中央的笼子里
They put him in a box out in the middle of the yard,
让他自生自灭
All by himself.
我无能为力
He can't do anything.
事情会好转的
It's going to be okay.
只会更糟
It's not going to be okay.
我不知道该如何是好
I don't know what to do, man.
事情已经乱套了
Everything's just fallen apart.
你在看什么?
What you lookin' at?
风景
The view.
我不禁发觉
I can't help but notice
你和勒齐成了朋友
You and Lechero made friends.
他最近跟很多白种人
He's been hanging out
混在一起
With a lot of white boylately.
-有问题吗? -没有 但是萨米有
Got a problem with that? no. but Sammy does.
听着 我最近仔细观察
See, I've been looking close,
就像一直以来一样
Like I always do.
而且我知道你们会很高兴
And I know you all would be a lot better off
如果萨米可以消失
If Sammy were no longer around.
那就不用去担心
Wouldn't have to worry
他敏锐的嗅觉坏了你们的好事
About his snout poking in your business.
那么你的建议是?
And you're suggesting ?
你我都明白 这事势在必行
You and I both know it needs to happen
索纳中没有多少人愿意冒险除掉萨米
There aren't many men in Sona who would take out Sammy.
我心中有个合适人选
I have one particular man in mind.
他欠我的
A man who owes me.
但是事成之后 我要求入伙
But if I pull through, I'm in the club, guaranteed.
你等着瞧好了
You're gonna see to it.
好吧 走着瞧
All right.
我想这笔交易你能做主
I assume you have the power to make this deal.
没错
I do.
成交
Agreed.
好了
Right.
那么
Well.
谢谢了
Thank you, sir.
听着 你跟我说的我想了很久
Look, I've been thinking about what you told me and, uh
但是我不能放弃这份工作
But I can't quit my job.
随你便吧
Do whatever you want to do.
如果你能借我点儿现金 我就放弃这工作
Well, I would if you could kick me a few bucks, you know.
我们还需要废话吗? 我告诉过你了
Are we gonna do this again? I told you.
我没有现金
I don't have any cash.
你希望我怎么做?
What do you expect me to do?
随你便
Do whatever you want.
你需要我的帮助 不是吗?
You could use my help, right?
你居然为友谊收费?
You're gonna start charging me now for your friendship?
还有个孩子等着我
I got a kid on the way
我的孩子可能再也见不到了
And I got a kid I may never see again.
喂 帮我接通格雷琴
Yeah, get me Gretchen.
让我很惊讶的是
Much to my surprise,
你的天方夜谭居然有些是真的
Therseems to be some degree of truth to your tale.
所有一切
Everything
我告诉你的都是真实的
I told you is true.
这点我自己会判断
That's for me to determine.
那我还能说什么?
What more can I say?
那个囚犯
This inmate.
就是你想帮他越狱的家伙
The one who you've been sent to free.
他会来证实你跟我说的一切
He should be able to verify what you've told me.
他确实可以 但是我不知道他是否愿意
He should but I don't know if he will.
告诉我他的名字
Tell me his na
这些家伙会毫不犹豫地杀了我侄子
These pele won't hesitate to kill my nephew.
我需要确定你真会竭力去找他
I need to know you're gonna do everything you can to find him.
-我会的 我需要那人的名字 -你发誓
I will, but I need a name. I need your word.
我发誓我会去找到那男孩
You have it. I'll find the boy.
现在告诉我那人的名字
Now, the name.
怎么了?
What's wrong?
你为何不告诉我?
Why don't you tell me?
我去过了那个寓所
I went to that apartment,
你的寓所
Your apartment.
那个女人出现了 显得很了解你
And this woman showed up like she knew you.
我发现了本护照
And then I found a passport.
谁是格雷·米勒?
Who's gray Miller?
那间寓所
That apartment,
那本护照
That passport,
都是为我们准备的
It's all for us.
当我离开这鬼地方后
It's how we're gonna get away.
这些都是为我们准备的后路
When I get out of this place,
我会找个可以长相思守的方式工作
I'll be working on a way for us to be together.
还记得我们一直说起的法国吗?
Remember how we always talked about france?
詹姆斯
Oh, James.
是的
Yeah.
我们团聚的计划啊
Our plan to be together.
詹姆斯 你让我怎么相信你?
James, how how can I believe you?
我怎么再相信任何事情?
How can I believe anything anymore?
惠斯勒
Whistler.
只要知道
And just know,
知道我爱你就行
Just know that I love you.
你即将面临一些严厉的指控
You're facing some serious charges.
迈克·斯科菲尔德告诉我说
Michael scofield told me
牢外有人
There are some people out there
下定决心要弄你出去
Who are very determined to get you out of here.
他说这话什么意思?
What's he talking about?
你对此一无所知?
You know nothing about this?
不知道
No.
斯科菲尔德是个聪明人 不过
Scofield's a smart man but, uh,
他有狂想症
He's got a rabid imagination.
所以你是想说他在撒谎?
So you're calling him a liar?
差不多吧
More or less.
我有能力去验证整件事的真假
I've been able to verify the story.
我早就知道了所有事情
I already know everything,
惠斯勒先生 是每个细节
Mr. Whistler, in detail.
我只需要你报个名字
I just need a name.
外头是谁在负责?
Who's in charge on the outside?
如果你现在开口的话 这事就算结了
We can end this right now if you can provide it.
不知道你什么意思?
What are you talking about?
你们要干吗?
What's going on here?
有劳了
Gracias.
现在
Now,
开始了
Start over.
你在这儿啊
There you are.
我来了
And here I am,
没给你带好货来
Without my bag of goodies.
我很担心你会一走了之 再不回来
I was afraid you were gone for good.
少了你 这戏就不精彩了
Party would not be the same without you.
很高兴你回来了 因为需要帮个忙
I'm glad you're back, cause I need a favor.
关系到你
It involves you,
一个鸡爪 还有一个找你的人
A chicken foot and a man who's got it comin'.
-谁? -萨米
What man? Sammy.
现在 你准备好 在角斗场打败他
Now, you get well, and you get him out there in that ring,
然后像这样 扭扭脖子
And you do that one, that neck thing.
作为回报
In exchange,
我可以给你所有毒品开销免单
I'm gonna cover all your medical expenses.
对话结束 你自己把握
I'll tell you what. you take your time.
我现在就拿包去
I'm gonna go get my bag right now,
杀了他 一了百了
Put you out of this misery.
阿历克斯 你是最擅斗的勇士
You're the best cock in the fight, Alex.
别让我失望
Please don't let me down.
或许这样你感觉更舒服些
Maybe now you'll feel more comfortable
愿意告诉我真相
Telling me the truth.
你和斯科菲尔德合谋的吗?
Are you working with Scofield?
是的 我和斯科菲尔德合谋的
Yes yes, I'm working with Scofield.
但是再也没有第三人卷入了
But there's no one else involved.
俗话说得好 真相终将
As they say in america, we're gonna get this story
大白于世
Straight.
我告诉他了真相
I told him the truth.
我猜想你也这么做了
I suggest you do the same.
是的 我说了
I have.
他什么也没有招供
He's confirmed nothing
问问那个一直和他碰面的女人的事
Ask him about that woman he's been meeting with.
并非如你所想那样
That's not what you think.
我怎想无所谓 要紧的是你知道什么
Doesn't matter what I think; it matters what you know,
你知道她的名字
And you know her name.
还有他不愿承认的事实
And the fact that he won't admit it
告诉我在这整件事情中
Tells me that he's no
-他根本不是无辜的旁观者 -你知道我是无辜的
Innocent bystander in this. you know I am.
那就证明看看 这是离开这的唯一方法
Prove it. 'cause that's the only way we're getting out of here.
迈克 这么做就是自杀
Michael, this is suicide
他们会杀了索菲亚
They'll kill Sofia.
-也会杀了你侄子 -这个人
And they'll kill your brother's son. this is the man
可以帮助我们 但是没有名字
Who can help us, and he can't do anything
他什么也办不到 快说出来吧
Without a name, so tell him
詹姆斯
James
我们没得选
We don't have a choice.
一切都结束了
It's over.
格雷琴·摩根
Gretchen morgan.
我不知道她住哪
I don't know where she lives,
也不知道如何能找到她
I don't know how you find her.
我只知道她叫
That's all I know, her name.
格雷琴·摩根
Gretchen morgan.
请再来两杯
Two more of those, please.
我要走了
Uh-uh. I'm gonna get going.
别呀 他不走
No, he'll stay.
放松点
Relax
是费尔南多吧
Fernando, is it?
我只想和你聊聊
I just want toalk a minute.
单独
Alone.
就这儿么
This right here
就咱们俩在这聊
Is as alone as we're gonna get.
我听说你和林肯的协议了
I heard about your argument with Lincoln.
你的人真是无处不在呀
You people are everywhere, huh?
现在 你比我更了解他
Now, you know him better
但根据我的经验
Than I do, but from personal experience,
布鲁斯很难对付
Burrows can be hard tndle.
那家伙总是说一套做一套
That man does not like to be told wt to do.
他喜欢指挥周围的每一个人
He sure likes bossing everyone else around.
你也该为自己
You have to start looking out
打算打算了 费尔南多
For yourself, Fernando.
逢场作戏一下吧
Level the playing field.
你该回去向他道歉
All you have to do is go back, apologize,
告诉他你会为了自由继续跟进
Tell him tha you'll stay on
一段时间
A few more days for free.
明天或者后天
And tomorrow or the day after,
我会电话你 咱俩再来喝一杯
I'll call you, and you'll meet me for a drink.
作为交换 我会付钱给你
In exchange, I'll pay.
5万怎么样
50 grand.
我知道你怎么想
I know what you're thinking,
但我不会要求你做任何事
But I'm not asking you to do anything
从长远看这没什么好处
That doesn't help everyone in the long run.
我不知道这会有什么帮助
i don't see how this is helping.
林肯制造了许多麻烦
Lincoln causes as many problems as he solves.
他需要改变下做事的方法
He needs to get out of his own way, and I think
我想你能帮他
You can assist him.
进一步说
I stay one step ahead,
你会得到5万
And you get 50 grand.
我不知道
I don't know.
我想你会办到
I think you do.
她就在巴拿马城的某处
She's somewhere here in panama city.
拜托 巴拿马城有一百万人呀
Aw, that's not much help in a city of a million people.
这要花多少时间
It could take days, weeks.
我说了 我只知道她的名字
I've told you. I only know her name.
-我没有别的办法了 -我有
I have no idea. I do.
我想用下你的电话
But I'll need to use your phone.
林肯
Linc.
迈克 你拿什么电话打的?
Michael what phone are you on?
听我说就行了
Just listen to me.
我想知道下一次你何时何地
I need to know where and when
与苏珊碰面
Your next meeting with Susan b is.
一小时后在加菲尔德酒吧 咋了?
Garfield-price building downtown in an hour. why?
加菲尔德酒吧 一小时后
Garfield-price, one hour.
你能给我带个口信吗?
Can you give her a message for me?
-可以 -告诉她一切都在按计划进行
Yeah. tell her everything is going as planned.
到底怎么了 迈克
What the hell's going on, Michael?
就这么告诉她就行 林肯
Just give her the message, Linc.
再见
I'll see you soon.
食物送到了
La comida llego.
你该应战了
You should have listened.
你想把一只鸡脚
Are you going to throw down a chicken foot
扔到泥水里(向我挑战)?
Over a puddle of puke?
你该被修理了
You should have mopped.
废物 还没轮到你
Stumpy, wait your turn, man.
打扰下
Excuse me.
我想向老大勒齐求助
I wanto see patron Lechero, por favor.
你找他有什么事?
What you want to see him about?
他给了我这个
I got one of these from him,
我没怎么着呀
And I didn't do nothing.
他听不懂
He don't listen.
决斗会按约定进行
The fight goes on as planned
我们午餐用完了就开始
After we eat lunch.
萨米
Sammy.
你安排的决斗?
You issue a fight?
对
Yeah.
有什么不妥?
What about it?
这不在你的权利范围内
It's not your right.
这不是你的地盘
It's not your place.
也许将会是
Well, maybe it should be.
她到了?
She's arrived?
我正在路上
I'm on my way.
最好你是对的
You'd better be right.
怎么了?
What happened?
起作用了
It worked.
真的
It did?
对 和你说的一样她来找我
Yeah. she came up to me just like you said
许诺下一大笔钱
And offered me a bunch of cash
让我监视你
To talk behind your back.
那我们还按计划进行吧
So we stick with the plan, right?
-当然 -酷
Yeah. cool.
我现在就去见她
I'm going to see her right now.
没事了
It's okay.
我来了
I came back for you.
振作起来 一切都会好的
Come on, now, everything's gonna be okay.
你不能这样毁了自己
You can't deprive yourself like this.
滚一边去
G-get out of here.
你还不明白吗
You don't mean that.
是的 我明白
Yeah yeah, I do.
我明白
I do.
直说吧
Talk straight.
你别老磨唧
You're not talking straight.
吸毒是死路一条
Withdrawals are the worst way to die.
你会发抖 会流汗不止
You're going to shake, and you'll sweat
直到死无葬身之地
Until you evaporate into nothing.
这将是一条痛苦的地狱之路
It's a long bumpy road to hell.
你想要什么 阿历克斯 想活吗
Is that what you want, Alex? or do you wanna live?
那地狱见吧
See you on the other side.
当你整夜不眠
When you're up all night
腹泻不止
With diarrhea
跑都跑不动的时候
Running down both your legs
你头发上沾满呕吐物
And vomit is in your hair
可别后悔
don't come crawling back.
真是漫长的一天
It's been a long day.
让这一切都结束吧
Let's just get this over with.
我帮我弟弟带个口信
I got a messe from my brother.
一切都在按计划进行
Everything is going ahead as planned.
真的? 我还以为你们遇到了大的挫折了呢
Really? I would think you'd be facing a major setback.
你了解迈克的
You ow Michael.
总是会有主意
Always has things worked out.
不 我不了解
No, I don't.
在我看来他总是没事找事
Seems to me he keeps screwing things up.
他做事情可比你想的全面多了
He's getting things do a whole lot faster than you.
惠斯勒明天出来 对吗
Whistler's out by tomorrow, all right?
格雷琴·摩根?
Gretchen morgan?
是我
Yes.
监狱总管萨瓦拉 巴拿马警察
General Zavala, panamanian national police.
-请和我们走一趟 -为什么 出什么事情了
Come with us, please. why? what's this all about?
-带走 -不 我不理解
Llevenla. no, I don't understand.
-我不理解 等等
I don't understand. wait
我和这事无关
I had nothing to do with this.
I had nothing to do with this
无关
Nothing
你可以否认卷入了
You're denying that you are involved
索纳监狱的越狱未遂事件
With escape attempts at Sona prison.
我从没到过这儿
I have never been here before in my life.
你没有见过任何关押在这儿的人?
And you've never met any of the men incarcerated here
-不 -那詹姆斯·惠斯勒呢?
No James Whistler?
-没有 -你知道我在说什么吗?
No. you know what I've been told?
从犯人那里? 可以想象
From prisoners? I can only imagine.
我听说你是
I've been told that you are
越狱事件的幕后主使者
The mastermind behind a prison escape
你绑架了一个男孩做人质
And that you've kidnapped a boy as collateral.
有吗?
Really?
我只是个侨民
Am I an alien?
我犯罪了吗?
Did I shoot jfk?
先生 我不认识詹姆斯 威尔逊
Sir, I have no idea who this James Wilson
-惠斯勒 -是谁
Whistler. is
我只是在这里度假
I'm just here to relax
再一年我就要回国
Before I have to go back to another year
给新来的学生教授社会学课程
Of teaching social studies to freshman idiots.
你是这的观光客?
You are a tourist?
我不是观光客 先生
No, not a tourist, sir.ere?
我乐意把自己当作生命的学者
I like to think of myself as a"student of life."
生命的学者
"a student of life"?
打开水管
Abre la manguera
他说什么
What did he say?
打开水管
"turn on the hose."
打呀 打呀 打呀
Fight fight fight
我再给你一次机会
I'm going to give you one chance.
是你策划了索纳监狱的越狱事件吗
Did you order the escape from Sona penitentiary?
是还是不是?
Yes or no?
到底是不是
貌似你很关心她
You seem concerned for her.
我们的未来在她手里
She holds our entire future in her hands.
所以我在乎
Ah, I'm concerned.
是不是
Yes or no?
不是
No
你证明了一件事
You've proven one thing.
这不是你第一次这样做了
this is not your first time.
跟我来
Come with me.
你认识这些人吗?
Do you know either of these men?
我从来没见过他们
I've never seen them before.
你撒谎
That's a lie.
我绝对没有见过他们
I've never seen them before in my life.
你什么时候见过她 在哪里?
Where and when have you seen her?
她来监狱探望过他 对吗?
She came to see him in visitation, isn't that right?
这是你以前的老板吗?
Is this the woman you work for?
是她策划了越狱事件吗?
Did she order the prison escape?
是不是?
Yes or no?
是的
Yes.
好的
All right,
很好
All right.
你是主谋之一?
You're the one in charge?
不是 我对越狱事件毫不知情
No. I don't know anything about a prison escape.
我只是个办事的
I'm just the baby-sitter.
按指令行事
I watch the kid.
那他在哪?
Where is he?
在帕洛玛附近
Near Paloma.
2号高速公路
Highway 2.
我可以带你去
I can take you.
把他们带回我的办公室
Take them back to my office.
把这个女的带到车里
Put the girl back in the car.
我们准备上路
We're going on a drive.
是你吗?
Was it you?
是你杀了莎拉?
Did you kill Sara?
我不知道你在说什么
I have no idea who you're talking about.
我不会放过你的
I'm coming for you.
万岁
Yeah
好吧
Yes. yes.
祝贺你
Congratulations.
你就是传说中的拳王道格拉斯?
You're a regul buster douglas, aren't you?
可这是什么?
Hey, what is this?
为什么把这个塞在鼻子里
How'd you get that up there, huh?
哼
Mm-hmm.
就在这边
Right there.
在这边 他在这
Right there. he's in there.
在这?
In here?
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
我真的非常抱歉
I am so sorry.
希望他没事
I hope he's all right.
过来接我
Pick me up.
我在小木屋这里
I'm at the shack.
带点毛巾过来
Bring towels.
你好 林肯
Hi, Lincoln.
奥古斯特
Augusto.
见到你太好了
Good to see you.
谢谢你的烟
Yeah, thanks for the cigars.
你没有打开包看看吗
You didn open the package?
我今天没时间看它
I didn't get around to it today.
你需要做个选择
You need to make a choice.
勒齐大限在即
Lecho's days are numbered.
你同意吗?
You agree?
你知道怎么做了吧
Then you know what you need to do.
到目前为止你一直做的不错
You've done a good job far.
现在是动手的时候了
Now is the time to make a move.
你要保证
Prove yourself.
回去打开包裹
Go back in and open the package.
他们在这干什么?
What are they doing here?
他们被带到这儿问话
They were here for questioning
好吧
Come on.
咱们走
Let's go.
监狱总管怎么了
What happened to the general?
早上监狱总管死在在2号高速公路上
The general was found dead this morning off highway 2.
你们得回去监狱里了
You're going back inside.
节哀顺变
I'm sorry to hear that.
他看起来是个好人
He seemed like a nice man.
你回来做什么?
What you doing back here?
你要想出去就给我电话用用
If you still want to get out of here, I need your phone.
到里面去打
Go inside.
干吗?
What?
LJ怎么样?
how's LJ?
他很好
He's fine.
你知道吗 苏珊怒了
You know what? Susan's not.
他很好? 你确定吗?
He's fine? are you sure?
确定 我刚刚跟他通了电话
Yeah. I just got off the phone with him.
你干吗不告诉我事情的进展
Why didn't you tell me what was going on?
你的计划差点害死他
He could have died because of what you did.
惠斯勒还在我们手上
We've still got Whistler.
到目前为止我们很好
As long as we do, we're okay.
我得走了
I got to go.
看见布兰克了吗?
Hey, did you see Blanco?
他在这里走来走去像是老大
He's walking around like the landlord.
我想你说过勒齐会照看这里
I thought you said Lechero was going to take care of it?
他会的
He will.
他说过这话很久了
How long has he been saying that?
如果你和勒齐还想像以前那样
Look if you and Lechero want to go around
作威作福 那就试试看
Like an old married couple, fighting this way or that
也许你要在厨房里
Maybe you li it in the kitchen.
你小心点
Hey, you be careful.
做点什么吧
Then do something
否则你知道会有什么结果
Or the next thing you know,
你只是斯科菲尔德的一颗棋子
You're gonna be taking orders from Scofield.
有人什么都不想做了
Some people stop at nothing, huh?
是的
Uh
无论如何
Yeah. whatever.
至少我们回来了
At least we're back inside.
你想要什么已经显而易见了
Which of course is exactly what you wanted.
是吗?
Isn't it?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
你是在引狼入室
You let the fox into the henhouse.
你放弃格雷琴只有一个原因
The only reason you gave up Gretchen's name
所以她会卷土重来把你带出去
Was so she could come in and pull you out of the fire.
你想要我放弃她
You wanted me to give up her name.
你知道不会就这样结束的
You know it doesn't end with her.
我懂
Yeah, I do.
问题在于你怎么办?
The qutions how do you?
一个新来的怎么可能
How does a simple fisherman seem to know
知道这么多关于公司的事情
So much about the company?
当她回来的时候 她会
When she comes back, and she will
我该说什么
what am I gonna say?
你想不想这样做?
You gonna do this or not?
你可以给她肯定的答复
You can tell her the answer is yes.
不过一旦我们出去了
But once we're out, I consider
所谓人质
You collateral
就没有任何意义了
Nothing more.